Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audio Lab materials, 1962 -- 2003; UA136.004; 8.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Financial Aid For College: Is Money Available?, given by William F. Eastwood, 1985-10-10; UA136.004.026.00083; Eastwood, William F. (Case 26)
  - Iran's Evolving Foreign Policy, given by Richard W. Cottam, 1985-10-10; UA136.004.026.00084; Cottam, Richard W. (Case 26)
  - Nomenklatura: Soviet Leadership Today, given by Michael Voslenski, 1985-10-29; UA136.004.026.00085; Voslenski, Michael (Case 26)
  - Is the U.S. Losing its Credibility?, given by Kenneth Tomlinson, 1985-10-31; UA136.004.026.00086; Tomlinson, Kenneth (Case 26)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women Conference - Keynote address, 1985-11-01; UA136.004.026.00087 (Case 26)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women Conference - Session One, Different Economies: Different Problems for Women, 1985-11-01; UA136.004.026.00088 (Case 26)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women Conference - Luncheon session, Return Engagements, 1985-11-01; UA136.004.026.00089 (Case 26)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women Conference - Session Two, The Madwoman in the Attic: International and Clinical Perspectives, 1985-11-01; UA136.004.026.00090 (Case 26)
  - Western Feminism and Third World Women Conference - Session Three, Are All Issues Women's Issues?, 1985-11-01; UA136.004.026.00091 (Case 26)
  - Fraus and Artful Deception, given by Alexander Kaczmarczyk, 1 of 2, 1985-11-04; UA136.004.026.00092; Kaczmarczyk, Alexander (Case 26)
  - Fraus and Artful Deception, given by Alexander Kaczmarczyk, 2 of 2, 1985-11-04; UA136.004.026.00093; Kaczmarczyk, Alexander (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Opening session, 1 of 2, 1985-11-06; UA136.004.026.00094 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Opening session, 2 of 2, 1985-11-06; UA136.004.026.00095 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - U.S. Policy towards SE Asia, A Congressional Perspective, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00096 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - U.S. Bilateral Relations: Current Sit. And Future Pros., 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00097 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - U.S. Trade Policy towards SE Asia, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00098 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Economic Trends in U.S. and Implications for S.E. Asia, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00099 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Political Transition and Social Transformation in Singapore, 1 of 2, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00100 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Political Transition and Social Transformation in Singapore, 2 of 2, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00101 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Singapore's Second Industrial Revolution, 1985-11-07; UA136.004.026.00102 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Doing Business in Singapore, 1 of 2, 1985-11-08; UA136.004.026.00103 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Doing Business in Singapore, 2 of 2, 1985-11-08; UA136.004.026.00104 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Asia Pacific Region and Singapore, 1 of 2, 1985-11-08; UA136.004.026.00105 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference - Asia Pacific Region and Singapore, 2 of 2, 1985-11-08; UA136.004.026.00106 (Case 26)
  - Singapore Fletcher School Conference schedule and correspondence, 1985; UA136.004.026.00107 (Case 26)
  - Dark Side of the Communications Revolution, given by V. Vittachi, 1985-11-18; UA136.004.026.00108; Vittachi, V. (Case 26)
  - Strategic Defense Initiative, A Peace Shield or Invitation to Nuclear Winter, 1985-11-18; UA136.004.026.00109 (Case 26)
  - Roots of Western Contradictions, given by Jean Francois Revel, 1985-11-21; UA136.004.026.00110; Revel, Jean Francois (Case 26)
  - L'Irony dans le Contes de Voltaire, given by Heri Coulet, 1985-11-22; UA136.004.026.00111; Coulet, Heri (Case 26)
    Lecture in French
  - The Paradox of Masculinity, given by Donald Bell, 1985-12-02; UA136.004.026.00112; Bell, Donald (Case 26)
  - The Philippines Symposium, 1 of 2, 1986-01-28; UA136.004.026.00113 (Case 26)
  - The Philippines Symposium, 2 of 2, 1986-01-28; UA136.004.026.00114 (Case 26)
  - Breakthroughs in International Communications, given by Eugene F. Murphy, 1986-01-30; UA136.004.026.00115; Murphy, Eugene F. (Case 26)
    Executive Vice President, RCA. Olin Center Lecture
  - Politics and Literature in the Caribbean, given by Maryse Conde, 1986-02-03; UA136.004.026.00116; Conde, Maryse (Case 26)
    Introduction by VeVe Clark
  - U.S. and the World: Era of International Communications, given by Diana L. Dougan, 1986-02-06; UA136.004.026.00117; Dougan, Diana L. (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Terrorism: Historical and Cultural Perspectives, 1 of 3, 1986-02-28; UA136.004.026.00118 (Case 26)
    Coordinator: Sherman Teichman
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Terrorism: Historical and Cultural Perspectives, 2 of 3, 1986-02-28; UA136.004.026.00119 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Terrorism: Historical and Cultural Perspectives, 3 of 3, 1986-02-28; UA136.004.026.00120 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Political Violence and Terrorism in Middle East, 1 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00121 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Political Violence and Terrorism in Middle East, 2 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00122 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - The Search for an Appropriate U.S. Response, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00123 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Terrorism as a Political Strategy, 1 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00124 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - Terrorism as a Political Strategy, 2 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00125 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - U.S. Counterterrorism, Implications for World Order, 1 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00126 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - U.S. Counterterrorism, Implications for World Order, 2 of 2, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00127 (Case 26)
  - International Terrorism Symposium - U.S. Foreign Policy, Guerrillas and Terrorists, 1986-03-01; UA136.004.026.00128 (Case 26)
  - Life After Tufts, given by Sol Gittleman and Leila Fawaz, 1986-03-05; UA136.004.026.00129; Gittleman, Sol, 1934-; Fawaz, Leila (Case 26)
  - Olin Lecture, given by John D. Ong, 1986-03-27; UA136.004.026.00130; Ong, John D. (Case 26)
  - It's a Hard Way to Make an Easy Living, given by Joseph E. Levine, 1986-04-01; UA136.004.026.00131; Levine, Joseph E. (Case 26)
  - Living through Two World Wars, given by W. Houston Kenyon, Jr., 1986-04-10; UA136.004.026.00132; Kenyon, W. Houston Jr. (Case 26)
  - Memorial Service for Donald Ross MacJannet, given by Tufts Administrators, et al., 1986-04-16; UA136.004.026.00133; McLennan, Scotty; Mayer, Jean; Muldorf, Jennifer; Hunter, Howard; Simches, Seymour; Harris, Mary (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Keynote Address, Caspar W. Weinberger, 1986-04-16; UA136.004.026.00134; Weinberger, Caspar (Case 26)
    US Secretary of Defense
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Doctrines and Technoloies: A Retrospective Assessment, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00135 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Doctrine and Technology: The Strategic Offense-Defense Synergism, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00136 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Strategic Offense-Defense Mixes: The Impact on Arms Control, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00137 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - New Technologies and Space Doctrines, 1 of 2, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00138 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - New Technologies and Space Doctrines, 2 of 2, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00139 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Toward Integration: The Airland Battle, 1 of 2, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00140 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Toward Integration: The Airland Battle, 2 of 2, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00141 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - The Role of Maritime Forces and the Airland Battle, 1 of 2, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00142 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - The Role of Maritime Forces and the Airland Battle, 2 of 2, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00143 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Doctrines, Technologies, and Smaller Powers, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00144 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance: A Net Assessment, 1 of 2, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00145 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - The U.S.-Soviet Military Balance: A Net Assessment, 2 of 2, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00146 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference - Summation Panel, 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00147 (Case 26)
  - International Security Studies Fletcher School Conference agenda, 1986-04-16 -- 1986-04-18; UA136.004.026.00148 (Case 26)
  - Pilgrims to Cambodians: The American Immigrant Experience, given by Sol Gittleman, 1986-04-17; UA136.004.026.00149; Gittleman, Sol, 1934- (Case 26)
  - International Education and Business Transactions, given by Jeswald W. Salacuse, 1986-04-28; UA136.004.026.00150; Salacuse, Jeswald W. (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - Economics: Reinventing the Square Wheel, given by Benjamin J. Cohen, 1986-06-30; UA136.004.026.00151; Cohen, Benjamin J. (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - panel discussion, 1986-06-30; UA136.004.026.00152 (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - So What Else Is New? Continuities in American Social Policy, 1986-07-01; UA136.004.026.00153 (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - panel discussion, 1986-07-01; UA136.004.026.00154 (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - The Illusion of Congruent Values, given by Adda B. Bozeman, 1986-07-01; UA136.004.026.00155; Bozeman, Adda (Case 26)
  - Historical Consciousness in American Policy Formulation Fletcher Symposium - panel discussion, 1986-07-01; UA136.004.026.00156 (Case 26)
  - Installation of Dean Salacuse, Fletcher Convocation, 1986-07-18; UA136.004.026.00157 (Case 26)
  - U.S. Intervention in Central America: The People's Response, given by Howard Zinn, 1986-09-23; UA136.004.026.00158; Zinn, Howard (Case 26)
    Co-speakers: Kate Hoffman and Julie Meyer
  - Conference on Singapore, 1986-10-06; UA136.004.026.00159 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Fletcher School Conference, three days
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Opening address, given by the Hon. Thomas P. O'Neill III, 1986-10-10; UA136.004.026.00160; O'Neill, Thomas P. III (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session I: Theories, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00161 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 2: Continentalism: Its History and Current Application in Defense, 1 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00162 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 2: Continentalism: Its History and Current Application in Defense, 2 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00163 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 3: Economic Continentalism and Prospects of Liberalized Trade, 1 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00164 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 3: Economic Continentalism and Prospects of Liberalized Trade, 2 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00165 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 4: International Political Initiatives of States and Provinces, 1 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00166 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 4: International Political Initiatives of States and Provinces, 2 of 2, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00167 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Saturday Lunch, given by The Hon. Ian Scott, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00168; Scott, Ian (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Saturday Dinner, given by The Hon. Gil Remillard, 1986-10-11; UA136.004.026.00169; Remillard, Gil (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 5: Segmentation of Government Decision-making in Ottawa and Washington, 1 of 2, 1986-10-12; UA136.004.026.00170 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 5: Segmentation of Government Decision-making in Ottawa and Washington, 2 of 2, 1986-10-12; UA136.004.026.00171 (Case 26)
  - University Consortium for Research on North America: "Canada - U.S. Relations" - Session 6: Efforts at Diversification, 1986-10-12; UA136.004.026.00172 (Case 26)
  - Democracy and Dictatorship, A Symposium on Chile, 1 of 2, 1986-10-23; UA136.004.026.00173; Winn, Peter; Dorfman, Ariel; Bitar, Sergio (Case 26)
  - Democracy and Dictatorship, A Symposium on Chile, 2 of 2, 1986-10-23; UA136.004.026.00174; Winn, Peter; Dorfman, Ariel; Bitar, Sergio (Case 26)
  - Globescope II: Welcome, Introduction, and Forum Overview, 1986-10-24; UA136.004.026.00175 (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Continuation of Opening Session, 1986-10-24; UA136.004.026.00175a (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Keynote Address - Prospects for the Global Environment, 1986-10-24; UA136.004.026.00175b (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Choices, Responsibility and Ethics Bumpers Address, 1986-10-25; UA136.004.026.00175c (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: DeBotero Address, 1986-10-25; UA136.004.026.00175d (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Ruckelshaus Address; International Cooperation; Accepting the Challenge, 1986-10-25; UA136.004.026.00175e (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: The Environment and Sustainable Food, A Status Report on New England, 1986-10-26; UA136.004.026.00175f (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Toward a New Diplomacy; Plenary Session; Next Steps; Forum Closing - tape 1, 1986-10-26; UA136.004.026.00175g (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: Toward a New Diplomacy; Plenary Session; Next Steps; Forum Closing - tape 2, 1986-10-26; UA136.004.026.00175h (Case 27)
  - Globescope II: An International Forum agenda, 1986-10-24 -- 1986-10-26; UA136.004.026.00175i (Case 27)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1986, 1 of 2, 1986-10-29; UA136.004.026.00176 (Case 26)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1986, 1 of 2, 1986-10-29; UA136.004.026.00177 (Case 26)
  - Blacks and Jews, given by Julian Bond, 1986-11-04; UA136.004.026.00178; Bond, Julian (Case 26)
    African American Center Lecture.
  - European Community Trade Policy, given by Professor Jacques Pelkmans, 1986-11-04; UA136.004.026.00179; Pelkmans, Jacques Professor (Case 26)
    Staff, European Institute Of Public Administration. Charles F. Adams Lecture.
  - Diplomacy Comes Out of the Closet: The Impact of Communications Technology, given by Vernon A. Walters, 1986-11-10; UA136.004.026.00180; Walters, Vernon A. (Case 26)
    US Permanent Representative to the United Nations. Emhart Lecture
  - Security and Development Issues AIFLD, 1986-11-13; UA136.004.026.00181 (Case 26)
  - ARPAD, given by Uri Von Lazar Ra'Anan, 1986-11-24; UA136.004.026.00182; Ra'Anan, Uri Von Lazar (Case 26)
  - Lecture given by Fran Hosken, 1986-11-25; UA136.004.026.00183; Hosken, Fran (Case 26)
  - The Iran Crisis and Covert Action, 1 of 2, 1986-12-09; UA136.004.026.00184; Turner, Stansfield; Woodward, Bob; Rubin, Alfred P.; Schultz, Richard (Case 26)
  - The Iran Crisis and Covert Action, 2 of 2, 1986-12-09; UA136.004.026.00185; Turner, Stansfield; Woodward, Bob; Rubin, Alfred P.; Schultz, Richard (Case 26)
  - Security and Development Issues AIFLD, given by Dr. Richard E. Bissell, 1987-01-20; UA136.004.026.00186; Bissell, Richard E. (Case 26)
  - International Entrepreneurship, given by Fred J. Bolling, Jr., 1987-01-29; UA136.004.026.00187; Bolling, Fred J., Jr. (Case 26)
    President, Astroline Corp. Olin Center Lecture
  - The Channel Tunnel, given by Jean-Loup Dherse, 1987-02; UA136.004.026.00188; Dherse, Jean-Loup (Case 26)
    Chief Executive, Eurotunnel. Olin Lecture Series
  - International Business, given by Walter H. Beglinger, 1987-02-26; UA136.004.026.00189; Beglinger, Walter H. (Case 26)
    Olin Lecture
  - Russian Poet Andrei Voznesensky, 1 of 2, 1987-03-26; UA136.004.026.00190; Voznesensky, Andrei (Case 26)
  - Russian Poet Andrei Voznesensky, 2 of 2, 1987-03-26; UA136.004.026.00191; Voznesensky, Andrei (Case 26)
  - Arms Control Conference, 1 of 3, 1987-03-27; UA136.004.026.00192; Carnesale, Albert (Case 26)
  - Arms Control Conference, 2 of 3, 1987-03-27; UA136.004.026.00193; Flanagan, Stephen; Linenthal, Edward; Steiner, Steven; Ryan, R. (Case 26)
  - Arms Control Conference, 3 of 3, 1987-03-27; UA136.004.026.00194; Blacker, Coit; Clausen, Peter; Eichenberg, Richard; Mendelsohn, Jack; Gainsborough, P. (Case 26)
  - International Relations, given by Ted Turner, 1987-04-02; UA136.004.026.00195; Turner, Ted (Case 26)
    Fletcher School Lecture. Cabot Auditorium
  - Role of Law in Future International Organizations, given by George Ali Saad, 1987-04-07; UA136.004.026.00196; Saad, George Ali (Case 26)
  - Lecture given by Michael S. Dukakis, 1987-04-09; UA136.004.026.00197; Dukakis, Michael S. (Case 26)
  - Guatemala: Politics of Genocide, given by Elena Ixcot and Beatriz Monz, 1987-04-13; UA136.004.026.00198; Ixcot, Elena; Monz, Beatriz (Case 26)
  - Transatlantic Economic Relations, given by Hon. J. Robert Schaetzel, 1987-04-16; UA136.004.026.00199; Schaetzel, J. Robert (Case 26)
  - ISS Conference, given by Jeanne Kirkpatrick, 1987-04-22; UA136.004.026.00200; Kirkpatrick, Jeanne (Case 26)
  - Lecture given by Elliot Richardson, 1987-04-27; UA136.004.026.00201; Richardson, Elliot (Case 26)
  - Dedication of Blakely Hall, 1987-09-09; UA136.004.026.00202 (Case 26)
  - Fletcher School Convocation, 1987-09-09; UA136.004.026.00203 (Case 26)
  - Nutrition Lecture: Coping with Drought in Kenya, given by John Field, 1 of 2, 1987-09-24; UA136.004.026.00204; Field, John (Case 26)
    Lecture One In Famine Lecture Series, School Of Nutrition.
  - Nutrition Lecture: Coping with Drought in Kenya, given by John Field, 2 of 2, 1987-09-24; UA136.004.026.00205; Field, John (Case 26)
  - Love and Anarchy: Italian Film Class, given by Jeanne Dillon, 1987-09-24; UA136.004.026.00206; Dillon, Jeanne (Case 26)
    Lecture on the film Love and Anarchy
  - Nutrition in Developing Countries, given by Nevin Scrimshaw, 1987-09-28; UA136.004.026.00207; Scrimshaw, Nevin (Case 26)
  - Corporate Restructure, given by Peter Ackerman, 1987-10-08; UA136.004.027.00001; Ackerman, Peter (Case 27)
    C. F. Adams Lecture, Fletcher School.
  - Famine Seminar Series lecture given by Barbara Thomas, 1 of 2, 1987-10-22; UA136.004.027.00002; Thomas, Barbara (Case 27)
    School of Nutrition
  - Famine Seminar Series lecture given by Barbara Thomas, 2 of 2, 1987-10-22; UA136.004.027.00003; Thomas, Barbara (Case 27)
  - After the INF Treaty, given by Martin Hillenbrand, 1987-11-19; UA136.004.027.00004; Hillenbrand, Martin (Case 27)
    Former US Ambassador to Germany
  - Coping with Famine in Ethiopia, given by Dr. Mesfin, 1 of 2, 1987-12-10; UA136.004.027.00005 (Case 27)
  - Coping with Famine in Ethiopia, given by Dr. Mesfin, 2 of 2, 1987-12-10; UA136.004.027.00006 (Case 27)
  - Steroids and Sports, given by Dr. John Kulig, 1988-01-26; UA136.004.027.00007; Kulig, John Dr. (Case 27)
  - Famine seminar, given by Christine Okali, 1 of 2, 1988-01-28; UA136.004.027.00008; Okali, Christine (Case 27)
    Oxfam representative. Famine Seminar Series
  - Famine seminar, given by Christine Okali, 2 of 2, 1988-01-28; UA136.004.027.00009; Okali, Christine (Case 27)
  - Race and Gender in Teaching, given by Gerald Gill, 1988-02-17; UA136.004.027.00010; Gill, Gerald R. (Case 27)
    Professor, Tufts History Department
  - The United States Maritime Dilemma: The Reason, The Remedy, given by Ole Skaarup, 1988-02-18; UA136.004.027.00011; Skaarup, Ole (Case 27)
    Chairman, Skaarup Shipping Corporation
  - Problems of Practice Before International Court, given by Keith Highet, 1988-02-25; UA136.004.027.00012; Highet, Keith (Case 27)
  - Teaching, given by Dale Bryan, 1988-03-02; UA136.004.027.00013; Bryan, Dale (Case 27)
    Peace and Justice Program
  - Addressing Gay Sexual Issues, given by Elderman, Lee, 1988-03-16; UA136.004.027.00014; Elderman, Lee (Case 27)
  - Latin American Debt: Keynote address and Panel 1, 1988-04-06; UA136.004.027.00015; Ramos, Joseph; Cohen, Benjamin; Krugman, Paul; Terrell, Henry; Thornblade, James; Devlin, David (Case 27)
  - Latin American Debt: Panel 1, part 2, 1988-04-06; UA136.004.027.00016; Ramos, Joseph; Cohen, Benjamin; Krugman, Paul; Terrell, Henry; Thornblade, James; Devlin, David (Case 27)
  - Latin American Debt: Special address and Panel 2, 1988-04-06; UA136.004.027.00017; Moreira, Marcilio Marques; Paddock, James; Cohen, Benjamin; Flannery, Dennis; Flores, Jose Luis; Hunt, Shane (Case 27)
  - Asian American Studies, given by Liz Toupin, Ruth Hsiao, and Reed Ueda, 1988-04-15; UA136.004.027.00018; Toupin, Liz; Hsiao, Ruth; Ueda, Reed (Case 27)
  - Key Approaches to Meet the Challenges of the Engineering and Construction Industry in the 1990s, given by Cordell Hull, 1988-04-27; UA136.004.027.00019; Hull, Cordell (Case 27)
  - Hallowell Dedication Speeches, 1988-05-20; UA136.004.027.00020 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 1 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00021 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 2 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00022 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 3 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00023 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 4 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00024 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 5 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00025 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 6 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00026 (Case 27)
  - Conference: A New Model for American Studies: Using Black, Ethnic, and Feminist Studies to Integrate the Sciences and Humanities, 7 of 13, 1988-06-09 -- 1988-06-12; UA136.004.027.00027 (Case 27)